♪Beneath the mask♪
♪Lies another mask♪
(Original Story: Haishi Lisheng)
♪Who's sincere♪
♪Who's only pretending♪
♪Borrowing your light♪
♪I walk through my own night♪
♪You are my weakness♪
♪And my weapon too♪
♪Draped in your shadow♪
♪I walk the blade's edge♪
♪If one day♪
♪The mask shatters♪
♪Will you still♪
♪Recognize my light♪
=The Masked Lover=
(Lu Zhentian)
=Episode 2=
(Weren't you supposed to silence her?)
(Why did you bring her back?)
(From now on,)
(she's on our side.)
(Can she pull it off?)
(When have I ever misjudged anyone?)
Butler Zhou.
Begin the ancestral rite.
Congratulations, Governor.
Your long-lost pearl has returned.
(Ancestral rite.)
(With our ancestors as witness,)
(and our clan elders gathered here,)
(a long-lost descendant of the Lu clan)
(has finally returned.)
(With our ancestors' blessing,)
(this is a joyous day for our family.)
(Ms. Lu.)
(You still haven't told me the mission.)
(The Lu family has a family heirloom.)
(Your mission is to become
the person Lu Zhentian is closest to)
(Lu Yutang)
(and trusts most in this world.)
(Make him willingly
pass the family heirloom on to you.)
(Lu Zhentian has a son.)
(Why pass it on to a daughter?)
(He has no son.)
(Lin Kefu was Lu Zhentian's only child.)
(Adjutant He, that's
where you're wrong.)
(You should say)
(I'm supposed to be Lu Zhentian's
only child.)
(Save your wit and clever tricks
for the mission.)
(Lu Zhentian is vicious, ruthless)
(Lu Yutang | Lu Yuran)
(and deeply calculating.)
(You won't fool him with petty tricks.)
(You still haven't told me)
(what exactly
the Lu family heirloom is.)
(Lu Yutang)
(A treasure map.)
(It leads to gold bars worth
a city's fortune.)
(Lu Yutang of the Lu Clan of Fancheng)
(hereby rejoins the family.)
(Loyalty Eternal)
♪That familiar wicked streak♪
Father, please have some tea.
My girl.
Get up.
Thank you, Father.
Where's Shaoyun?
Here I am.
It's just a daughter.
Incense, tea, all this ceremony.
Is all this really necessary?
Kefu.
Who did this to you?
Lu Shaoyun is the killer.
(I never thought I'd face my enemy)
(so soon.)
(He's lecherous. Perfect.)
(My enemy's lust gives me an opening.)
So you really are my sister?
Did you check everything?
She'd better not be an impostor.
Remember.
You should resist accepting
this new sister
who appeared out of nowhere.
Got it.
Quit fooling around.
Sit down.
I'm just joking, Father.
My girl, serve your brother some tea.
All right.
Brother, please have some tea.
Brother, I'm sorry.
Father.
My sister is too reckless.
Looks like she needs some discipline.
Is that any way to talk to your sister?
I keep telling you to read more.
You're so uncultured.
Enough.
Tonight,
let's have a family reunion dinner.
Having a powerful father is pretty nice.
Both bags look great.
I like them both.
You may go.
- Yes.
This dress is the prettiest.
I'll wear it when I see Father tonight.
What do you think, Adjutant He?
Nothing special.
As long as I like it.
(Afraid to die.)
(Vain.)
(Fawning.)
(Someone like her makes)
(the perfect pawn.)
(Even without He Jingchen's mission,)
(to stay at the Governor's Residence,)
(I'd still have to win
Lu Zhentian over.)
(What kind of daughter would he like?)
Even as the young lady of
the Governor's Residence,
you should knock before entering
someone else's room.
I came to borrow something from you.
What?
Why do you need the military uniform
I wore as a child?
For a magic trick.
Weren't you the one who promised
to give me your full support?
Your sister will be here soon.
Act like a proper brother.
Lu Yutang of the Lu Army,
reporting for duty.
You little rascal.
You look quite the part.
Come.
Sit.
Father.
Though I didn't grow up by your side,
your reputation is legendary.
You're the person I admire most
in all of Fancheng.
Speaking of which,
I had a roomful of Western dresses
prepared for you.
Where did that uniform come from?
I conjured it up.
I'm your daughter.
Of course I want to be like you
and become Fancheng's guardian deity.
Good.
Pour the wine.
Have a drink with me.
Come.
Let's drink as a family.
- Come on.
- Cheers.
Quite the old drunk.
He's met his match in the little one.
I'm going back to the study.
Keep an eye on things in there.
Another round!
Father, you can really hold your liquor!
Father.
Let me toast you again.
All right.
Tonight, we drink till we drop.
I'm so hot.
Easy now.
I'll take you back to your room.
Brother.
I like hearing that.
Say it again.
Brother.
(Kefu,)
(tonight,)
(I'll send your killer to you
to atone for what he did.)
(One Day Earlier)
(I don't even know my own birthday.)
(Just so we could share a birthday,)
(I insisted we had the exact same
date of birth.)
(Kefu,)
(we're finally eighteen.)
(We're adults now.)
(I never thought)
(death would part us so soon.)
(Kefu,)
(forgive me)
(for borrowing your identity)
(to avenge you.)
♪A lie carved deep into the heart♪
(Loyalty Eternal)
♪Blades clash, leaving us both trapped♪
♪Nightmares from days gone by♪
♪Love and hate intertwine♪
♪In eyes ignited by sparks♪
♪Each blooming with a fierce edge♪
♪Shattering moonlight on the ground♪
♪I look up and meet your gaze♪
♪Unveiling all the absurdity♪
♪Seeking love's only truth♪
♪Through fate's layered maze♪
♪Charging toward the unknown♪
♪Don't forget your stubborn heart♪
♪Fire tempers the strength to go on♪
♪Counting down the long night's haze♪
♪With my own hands, I draw the dawn♪
♪Boundless♪